[
  {
    "question": "GI Genius is an AI assisted _____ tool which is designed to detect polyps.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Colon", "Cancer", "Endoscopy", "Intestine", "Bowel"],
    "answer": "colonoscopy",
    "source": "https://www.virtua.org/news/virtua-health-launches-ai-technology-to-enhance-colon-cancer-screenings#:~:text=GI%20Genius%E2%84%A2%20helps%20physicians,women%20in%20the%20United%20States."
  },
  {
    "question": "Viz.ai's AI products can detect issues and notify _____ teams quickly, enabling providers to discuss options, provide faster treatment decisions, thus saving lives.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Tend", "Aid", "heed", "support", "concern"],
    "answer": "Care",
    "source": "https://builtin.com/artificial-intelligence/artificial-intelligence-healthcare"
  },
  {
    "question": "BioXcel Therapeutics, Inc. is a biopharmaceutical company utilizing artificial intelligence to develop transformative medicines in _________.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["neuron", "science", "brain", "nerves", "neurology"],
    "answer": "neuroscience",
    "source": "https://www.bioxceltherapeutics.com/overview/"
  },
  {
    "question": "PathAI is the only AI-focused technology company with comprehensive precision ______ solutions",
    "forbiddenWords": ["disease", "tissue", "lab", "biopsy", "diagnosis"],
    "answer": "pathology",
    "source": "https://www.pathai.com/about-us/"
  },
  {
    "question": "Activ Surgical completed the world’s first autonomous ______ surgery of soft tissue in 2018.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["robot", "machine", "Cyborg", "terminator", "Bionic"],
    "answer": "robotic",
    "source": "https://www.activsurgical.com/about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Butterfly Network revolutionizes medical imaging by creating the first hand-held whole-body _______ imager, paired with AI technology.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["sound", "MRI", "X-Ray", "echo", "Imaging"],
    "answer": "ultrasound",
    "source": "https://www.butterflynetwork.com/why-butterfly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cleerly's AI-based platform aids in diagnosing and treating ____ disease earlier by analyzing and characterizing plaque buildup.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["heartbeat", "Arteries", "blood", "pumping", "veins"],
    "answer": "heart",
    "source": "https://cleerlyhealth.com/heart-disease-technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "A form of AI known as Convolutional neural network has been shown to outperform experienced doctors in detecting ______ cancer, especially malignant melanomas.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["covering", "dermis", "largest", "dermatologist", "sensation"],
    "answer": "Skin",
    "source": "https://www.oncozine.com/artificial-intelligence-better-dermatologists-diagnosing-skin-cancer/"
  },
  {
    "question": "An AI framework developed by researchers aids in detecting errors in medication administration using devices such as _____ for patients with lung diseases.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Asthma", "Breathing", "Puff", "Respiratory", "Spray"],
    "answer": "Inhalers",
    "source": "https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-021-01273-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Johnson & Johnson MedTech is using AI in the development of their Monarch™ Platform for _______________",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Bronchoscopy", "Bruno", "Endoscopy", "Pulmonology", "Respiratory"],
    "answer": "Bronchoscopy",
    "source": "https://www.jnjmedtech.com/en-US/product/monarch-bronchoscopy"
  },
  {
    "question": "MIT group's ML algorithm contributes to the identification of cardiomegaly in chest X-rays found _____ approach gives the best result.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Hybrid", "Both", "Mixed", "Duel", "Merge"],
    "answer": "Hybrid",
    "source": "https://www.ibm.com/blog/the-benefits-of-ai-in-healthcare/"
  },
  {
    "question": "AI-powered chatbots are becoming increasingly common in healthcare for patient interactions. What is the term for these chatbots that assist patients in scheduling appointments and providing medical information?",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Chatbox", "Appointment", "Online", "Computer"],
    "answer": "Virtual Assistant",
    "source": "https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/role-artificial-intelligence-streamlining/"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can the AI system developed by researchers at Moorfields Eye Hospital and UCL Institute of Ophthalmology potentially predict, besides sight-threatening eye diseases?",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Arrest", "love", "stroke", "Cardiac"],
    "answer": "Heart Attack",
    "source": "https://europe.ophthalmologytimes.com/view/retfound-artificial-intelligence-model-to-detect-retinal-disease-biomarkers-developed-by-moorfields-eye-hospital"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for the AI application that uses computer vision to analyze medical images like X-rays and CT scans for diagnosis?",
    "forbiddenWords": ["AI", "Computer", "Vision", "Images", "X-rays", "scans"],
    "answer": "Radiomics",
    "source": "https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/oncology/articles/10.3389/fonc.2020.00342/full"
  },
  {
    "question": "IBM's ____ has received considerable attention in the media for its focus on precision medicine, particularly cancer diagnosis and treatment. It employs a combination of machine learning and NLP capabilities.",
    "forbiddenWords": ["What", "Son", "Healthcare", "Cloud"],
    "answer": "Watson",
    "source": "https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6616181/"
  },
  {
    "question": "AI is facilitating early disease detection by analyzing genetic information. _____ analysis is the term for this AI application that assesses genetic data to predict health risks?",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Genetics", "Prediction", "Disease", "Health"],
    "answer": "Genomic",
    "source": "https://genomemedicine.biomedcentral.com/"

  },
  {
    "question": "What is the potential drawback of overreliance on AI in clinical decision-making, where medical professionals may rely too heavily on algorithmic recommendations?",
    "forbiddenWords": ["Drawback", "Overreliance", "Algorithmic", "Recommendations"],
    "answer": "Depersonalization",
    "source": "https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7913310/"
  }

]
